紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   草草
時間軸   想念Gallifrey的wholock
后期   餓得慌
校對  草草
顧問  老杜
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第六季  第二集
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
謝潑德自由基金會
同意
總統親臨化學泄露事故現場
總統抽手了嗎
安德伍德尷尬握手時刻在網上瘋傳
你桌上有一份法案
There's a bill sitting on your desk.
這份法案耗時數年才獲得通過
A bill that took years to get passed.
你簽署了
You sign that,
我就知道我在白宮里有朋友
and I know I got a friend in the White House.
如果你不簽
If not...
那我就沒有
Then I don't.
這不是協商
This is not a negotiation,
這是最后通牒  簽署法案  否則
this is an ultimatum. Sign the bill or what?
否則什么
Or what?
-她中槍了嗎  -趴下  趴下
- Is she shot? - Stay down, stay down!
有人企圖殺她
Somebody tried to kill her.
比爾
Bill.
是你搞的嗎
Were you behind this?
我今天不會簽那個的
I won't be signing that today.
那是個錯誤
That was a mistake.
你聽命于誰
Who do you answer to?
你為誰工作
I mean, who do you work for?
或許該給他開抗精神病藥了
Well, maybe it's time to give him one of the antipsychotics.
生日快樂  美國
Happy Birthday, America.
不管弗蘭西斯這五年來對你們說了什么
Whatever Francis told you the last five years,
一個字都別信
don't believe a word of it.
他還在我們身邊  是吧
He's still with us, don't you think?
幸好他死前我們能跟他共度那么多的時光
We're so glad we got to spend so much time with him before he died.
他對我們說了些很有趣的事
He told us some fascinating things.
站住  克萊爾·黑爾
Stop. Claire Hale.
你想弗蘭西斯了嗎
Do you miss Francis?
我要你宣布  羅杰  我們好派他們去
I want a Declaration, Roger. So we can send them in.
但總統女士
But, Madam President--
國民警衛隊  聯邦緊急事務管理署和環保署
I have the Guard, FEMA and the EPA
都調動好了  就在城外等著
mobilized and waiting on the outskirts of that town.
我剛跟精煉廠聯系過
I just got off the phone with the refinery.
泄露已經要燒盡了
The leak is well on its way to burning off.
據我所知  空氣質量達到了危險程度
My understanding is that the air quality is dangerous.
污染的確加重了  是的
The levels are somewhat elevated, yes,
-但風向對我們有利  -但也可能變化
- but the winds are in our favor. - And subject to change.
風就是如此
That's how wind works.
一兩天內一切都會結束
This will all be over in a day or two,
但要讓民眾撤離家園...
the idea of keeping these families out of their homes--
這謹慎的預防措施
This is a prudent precaution
我坐鎮時  就希望采取這種措施
and on my watch, that's what I want to happen.
我覺得不應該夸大情況
I don't think we should exaggerate the situation.
你還記得選舉當晚你的情況嗎  州長
Do you remember where you were on election night, Governor?
我可記得
Because I do.
你本來要輸了
You were going to lose.
統計學上講  你是根本不該贏的
Statistically, there is no reason you should have won.
你考慮的時候
Keep the phone away from your mouth
別把電話靠在嘴邊  州長
while you're thinking, Governor.
我聽得到你的喘氣聲
I can hear you breathing.
是
Yes.
我覺得我是有必要宣布進入緊急狀態
I do believe I need to declare a state of emergency.
當然了  這是你的決定
Of course, it's your call.
我向你保證
And I assure you,
聯邦政府會全力支持你
you will have the full support of the federal government.
我曾對自己保證不會像他那樣
I promised myself I wouldn't be like him.
但那就是弗蘭西斯的典型做法  是吧
That was textbook Francis, wasn't it?
但他像遞鹽罐一樣把我交給了他們
But he handed me over to them like a shaker of salt
現在  他們不肯放手了
and now they won't let go.
這是他們自作自受
This is a wound of their own making.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President?
請進
Yeah, come in.
需要我等您一會兒嗎  先生
Do you need a moment, sir?
不用
No, no.
怎么了
What is it?
好
Okay.
州長
Governor?
他們說沒事的
They said it was fine.
就是一股爛雞蛋和垃圾的味兒
It smelled like rotten eggs and trash. That's all.
水龍頭里都是這個味兒
You could smell it coming out of the faucet.
然后我兒子  他開始流鼻血了  我就想
And then my son, his-- his nose started to bleed and I thought,
-"跟這有關嗎"  -你兒子現在在哪呢
- "Is that related?" - Where is your little boy right now?
現在嗎  他跟他媽在做驗傷
Now? He's in triage with his mom.
-那小家伙是我的心肝  -我知道
- He's my heart, that little guy. - No, I know. I know.
但女士  我可以問問嗎
But, ma'am. If I may. You--
您得告訴我們  這是不是真的
You have to tell us. Is this real or not?
因為  起初他們說我們不需要撤離
Because at first they said that we don't need to evacuate,
但突然又改口說得撤離
and then all of a sudden that we should.
我要告訴你  一切都會沒事的
I want you to know everything is going to be all right.
我保證
I promise you.
我們指望著那工廠通知我們情況呢
We were relying on that plant to keep us informed.
先生  你和你的安全
Sir, you and your safety
才是最重要的
is the most important thing.
事實上  貝爾波特所有的家庭
In fact, all of the families of Bellport,
才是唯一重要的
nothing else matters.
我要感謝奧姆斯泰德州長
I want to give my thanks to Governor Olmstead
他今早快速果決地
for his quick and decisive act this morning
宣布了進入緊急狀態
in declaring a state of emergency.
聯邦緊急事務管理署  環保署
We have FEMA, we have EPA,
俄亥俄州國民警衛隊
the Ohio National Guard.
都來了
They're all here.
沒有人應該感到不安全
No one should ever feel unsafe.
...在她自己家里
In her own home.
你怎么會完全不知道呢  馬克
And how is it you have no idea, Mark?
-這無所謂  -這很有所謂
- It doesn't matter. - Oh, it does matter.
這說明了我們的關系多靠不住
It speaks to this untenable arrangement.
我說了待會兒再說那個  先考慮回應
Later, I said. Let's stay focused on our response.
她今早本都已經要簽署法案了
She was all set to sign the bill this morning.
我們叫了攝像師和記者什么的候著
We had photographers, a press pool waiting, the whole thing.
-但她沒簽  是吧  -我這就過去
- But she didn't sign it, did she? - I'm on my way there now.
因為她在忙著
Because she was too busy
無中生有地制造緊急狀況
manufacturing an emergency out of nothing.
別忘了是誰升級了事態  好嗎
Look, let's not forget who escalated this. Okay?
什么
Excuse me?
如果我們要合作  比爾
If we're working together, Bill,
我需要參與每一個決定
I need to be included in every decision.
每一個
Every one.
我們沒什么好談的了
This conversation's over.
老天爺啊
Oh, for God's sakes.
我會去貝爾波特跟安奈特碰頭
I'll join Annette in Bellport.
不  你別去
No, you won't.
你們中有一人到場就夠糟了
One of you showing up on site is bad enough.
安奈特  給我打電話
Annette, call me back.
馬克
Mark.
馬克  你還在嗎
Mark, are you still there?
是的
Yes.
讓我跟他談談  我再打給你
Let me talk to him. I'll circle back.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
我是凱爾茜·斯圖爾特
My name is Kelsey Stewart.
代理新聞發言人
I'm the deputy press secretary,
今天我將為大家回答問題
and I will be taking your questions today.
莎拉
Sarah.
奧姆斯泰德州長是否真的
Is it true that Governor Olmstead
對宣布進入緊急狀態很抗拒
was resistant to declaring a state of emergency?
州長的確宣布了進入緊急狀態
The Governor did declare a state of emergency,
白宮也贊同了
and the White House concurs.
工廠出了很大的問題
Something very wrong happened in that plant.
請說
Yes.
阿卡斯公司在泄露和爆炸事件方面
Arcas has been slow to provide any details
遲遲不肯公布細節
when it comes to the leak and explosion.
更不用說兩人在事故中喪生了
Not to mention the two lives lost in the accident.
他們跟白宮配合了嗎
Have they been cooperating with the White House?
現在總統去了第一線
Now that the president is on the ground,
他們似乎是更加愿意配合了
it seems that, yes, they have been more agreeable.
但這不是該問的問題
That's not the real question, though.
該有人問問
Somebody might want to ask,
謝潑德無限責任公司怎么不出來說話
where is Shepherd Unlimited in all of this?
阿卡斯精煉廠是該家族集團的子公司
The Arcas Refinery is a subsidiary of the family's conglomerate.
你是說謝潑德家族
Are you saying that the Shepherds
清楚工廠的問題嗎
are personally aware of problems at the plant?
誰該負責  負怎樣的責任
Who is responsible and how
這正是白宮和總統
is all the White House and the president
此刻想要查清的問題
are trying to find out at this point.
這會對總統
Will this have any effect
準備簽署的去監管法案有影響嗎
on the regulatory bill on the president's desk?
總統不久后就會就此發表講話
The president will be speaking on that shortly.
馬可斯
Marcus.
總統在前總統死前
Was the president planning to divorce the former president
有打算與他離婚嗎
in the days leading up to his death?
我們...
Let's...
-副總統先生  -大家早上好
- Mr. Vice President. - Morning, everyone.
希望斯圖爾特小姐不會介意我回答幾個問題
I hope Miss Stewart won't mind me taking a couple of questions.
副總統先生  請回答一個問題
Mr. Vice President, one question!
馬可斯  你的消息源是誰
Marcus, who's your source?
-匿名官員  -不  這行不通了
- Unnamed officials. - Nope. We don't do that anymore.
我們要名字  你能說嗎
We need names. You have a name?
說真的  你是哪聽來的
I mean really, where do you get this?
前總統
The former president
生前的最后一晚
spent his last night alive
是在白宮他妻子身邊度過的  就是這樣
next to his wife in the White House. Period.
至于貝爾波特
As for Bellport...
知道全部事實之前  不要急著下結論
let's not jump to conclusions before all the facts are in.
還有什么
What else?
我們還在逐戶查看  但這只是為防萬一
We still going door to door, but it's really a precaution.
床位夠嗎
Are there enough beds?
我們有幾間教堂地下室
We have a few church basements
如果有必要  還有當地監獄
and the local jail if we need more.
反正空氣里還剩下的硫化氫
Whatever hydrogen sulfide there is left in the air
也要消散了
is already dissipating.
再過一兩天  大家就能回自己的床上睡覺
In a day or two, people will be back sleeping in their own beds.
您得明白
You have to understand,
總統女士
Madam President,
幾乎所有人都會對化學品過度反應
most everyone overreacts when it comes to chemicals.
我們有多年的經驗
We have years of experience--
那死于事故的人呢
And the men who died in the accident?
那的確很悲慘  他們都是好員工
That's tragic, of course. They were valued employees.
都是社區里的成員  他們不可替代
Members of the community. There's no way to replace them.
比爾·謝潑德呢
And Bill Shepherd?
-怎么  -他來過電話嗎
- Yes. - Have you heard from him?
我把情況通知了他和其他合伙人
I've kept him informed, as well as all of our partners.
比爾直接給我打過電話
Bill called me directly.
他們準備采取一切必要措施
They're ready to do whatever's needed.
他們對貝爾波特非常重要
They're important to Bellport.
他們建了當地的運動場
They built the local stadium.
還有這個體育館  他們出資...
Even this gymnasium. They contributed--
我很清楚他們家族的慈善事業
No, I'm well aware of the family's philanthropy.
我問的不是那個
That wasn't the question.
是的  謝潑德先生一直在密切關注局勢
Yes, Mr. Shepherd has been monitoring the situation closely.
我想在這一代巡視一圈
I would like to tour the area.
可以嗎  州長
Is that a problem, Governor?
當然  據我所知沒問題
No, no, not to my understanding.
我還想帶您去
I was hoping to get you over to--
我們的驗傷處
to where we set up our triage.
我們最好還是按日程來...
It might be best if we stick to the itinerary--
我想自己親眼看看
I'd actually like to see it for myself.
當然  除非你們說不行
Unless, of course, you tell me otherwise.
不  當然可以
No, of course not.
警衛隊標記了已撤離的房子
The guard marks the doors of the evacuees.
都是標準程序
Pretty standard procedure.
停車  我好像看到了人
Stop the car. I think I see someone.
停車
Stop the car.
總統女士  我們會叫人再回來的
Madam President, we'll have someone circle back.
馬上停車
Stop the car now.
該死
Damn it.
她安全嗎
Is she safe?
沒有百分之百的安全
Nothing is 100% safe.
有人嗎  有人在嗎
Hello. Anyone here?
那男孩差點瞎掉一只眼睛
The boy could have lost an eye.
我們不能那么對待別人
That's not how we treat people.
她怎么能這么做
How could she?
天吶  伊麗莎白  行了
My God, Elizabeth, stop it.
我養的是個女兒還是野獸
Am I raising a daughter or an animal?
他們才是野獸  他們那么攻擊她
They're the animals, the way they attacked her.
好啊  替她說話吧你就
Oh, of course, take her side. Of course!
她也該了解這世界了
It's time she learned about the world.
漂亮姑娘要對她們的美貌負責
Pretty girls have a responsibility to their beauty.
肯定是她激了那些男孩
I'll bet she dared those boys.
真丟臉
Shame on her.
你怎么就不能乖乖聽話
Why can't you just do as you're told?
是啊  為什么
Why, indeed?
總統女士  總統女士
Madam President! Madam President.
總統女士
Madam President...
我們最好回去了
might be best if we head back.
房子安全嗎
So, the house is safe?
那喝一口
Drink it then.
我猜也是
I thought so.
-但我在答應什么  -我可以給你讀一遍
- But what am I agreeing to? - I can read it for you.
我識字
I can read.
這是干什么的
And what's this for?
這是讓應用能分析出
That lets the app figure out
我們怎樣才能最好地施以幫助
how we can be most helpful.
可以根據你的具體需求來制定計劃
It can be tailored to your specific needs.
我們想讓你及時了解情況
We want to keep you informed.
我們希望你在事發前就知道要發生什么
We want you to know what happens before it happens.
這是不能靠政府的
You can't trust the government to do that.
你好  我是賽斯·格雷森
Hello, my name is Seth Grayson.
認識你很高興
Nice to meet you.
我是謝潑德自由基金會的
I'm with Shepherd Freedom Foundation,
可以跟你談談嗎
can I talk to you for a second?
當然  我看了宣傳冊
Sure thing. I was looking at the pamphlet saying just...
是總統
It's the president.
總統女士
Madam President.
是誰的主意  把戒指放他床上
Whose idea was it? To leave it on his bed?
別在這兒說
Not here.
謝潑德自由基金會是來幫忙的
The Shepherd Freedom Foundation is here to help.
聯邦政府將幫助你們
The federal government is here to help you.
是啊  總統女士
Yes, Madam President.
美國的問題要得到解決
The only way America's problems will be solved
就得靠政府和私企聯手
is through alliances between government and private industry,
各司其職
each doing its part.
我跟三軍統帥可是老交情了
The Commander in Chief and I go way back.
是啊  我知道謝潑德家族會
We do. And I know I have the full cooperation
完全配合我的工作
from the Shepherd family.
阿卡斯這種公司
The blatant disregard for human life
對生命的公然漠視...
exhibited by companies like Arcas--
阿卡斯公司是一心想保護其員工的安全的
Arcas is committed to the safety of its workers.
如果能得到助力
And with the help of...
比如正確的立法  像是《未來法案》
the right kind of legislation, like the FUTURE Act.
此刻正在接受審核
Which is under review at the moment.
法案通過前
Until then,
我要讓環保署的犯罪調查處
I am hereby moving the EPA's Criminal Investigative Division
進駐五角大樓
into the Pentagon,
他們將擁有軍隊的力量和資源支持
where it will enjoy the forces and the resources of our military.
他們會調查這起災難的
And they will investigate this disaster.
我以我丈夫的墳墓起誓
I swear on my husband's grave,
我一定會查明究竟發生了什么
I will find out what happened here.
謝謝您的支持
Thank you for your support.
我本想放在你床上呢
I wanted to leave it on your bed.
別犯傻  那對我沒用
Don't be thick, thick I can't use.
她真提出離婚了嗎
Did she actually ask for a divorce?
那要緊嗎
As if that matters.
如果我被要求給出這么問的憑據呢
And if I'm asked to justify the question?
他們不正面回答  就是足夠的憑據了
It was justified the moment they didn't have an answer.
總統最不希望
The last thing the president wants
談前總統的事了
is to be talking about the former president.
那我問問你
Let me ask you this.
總統甩開
How did your mother feel
你媽媽的手時  她是什么感覺
when the president yanked her hand away like that?
那不關你的事  馬可斯
That's none of your goddamn business, Marcus.
-抽手  你是這么說的嗎  -是啊
- Recoil? Is that the word you used? - Yeah,
我看就是這樣
that's what I see.
-開玩笑嗎  -不是
- Are you kidding me? - No.
我們真要浪費時間
Are we really gonna waste time
剖析兩個女人之間的一個手勢嗎
dissecting a gesture between two women?
諾拉說得對  我當時在場
Nora's right. I was there.
沒有什么抽手
There wasn't a recoil.
我同意湯姆的話
I gotta agree with Tom here.
我覺得安奈特·謝潑德是想硬拉著總統
For me, it's Annette Shepherd sort of manhandling the president
擺出勝利姿態  然后我看到她驚了一下
as a sign of victory, and then I detect a flinch.
就那么一下下  然后就抽了手
A slight flinch, then recoil.
-抽手...  -她是想切斷自己
- Recoil? I mean-- - She's trying to separate herself
跟原本計劃的弗蘭西斯·安德伍德基金會
from the primary source of the funding for what was to be
-主資金源的關系  -這是關于過失
- the Francis J. Underwood Foundation. - This is about culpability.
她是去貝爾波特要求責任方負責的
She went to Bellport to hold those responsible accountable.
謝潑德無限責任公司這樣的公司一直在被拖后腿
Companies like Shepherd Unlimited have been hamstrung.
所以她要簽署的法案才如此重要
And that's why this bill on her desk is so important.
如果不能執行  立法就毫無意義
Legislation means nothing without proper enforcement.
給環保署武器只是固執
Weaponizing the EPA is wrongheaded.
而且根本不能...
And it does nothing to make--
與其給她的每一個行為找負面動機
Instead of ascribing negative motives to her every action,
我們為什么不能承認  安德伍德總統
why can't we just accept that President Underwood
去做了總統該做的事
was out there being presidential?
她讓你
She put the fear of God
和你的新朋友感到害怕了  格雷森先生
into you and your new friends, Mr. Grayson.
做總統該做的事  就該簽署法案
Being "Presidential" means signing the bill
更新陳舊的監管
and modernizing antiquated regulations.
你怎么會知道
As if you would know.
那是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
她丈夫  你曾是他政府的成員
Her husband, whose administration you were a part of,
本來就要...
was about to--
正準備建立一個慈善基金會
Was in the midst of setting up a philanthropic foundation.
她丈夫都要被起訴了
Her husband was about to be indicted.
什么  八字沒一撇的事
Excuse me, there wasn't even a grand jury.
我有可靠消息稱
I have it on good authority
他要被起訴了  而她要赦免他
he was about to be indicted, and she was about to pardon him.
但她還想離婚
But she also wanted a divorce.
好挽救自己  撇清關系
To save herself. Distance herself.
因為  拜托  難道你能說
Because, come on. Are you telling me
她對他的作為一無所知嗎
she knew nothing of what he was up to?
-如果他有罪  她也有  -湯姆
- If he was guilty, she was guilty. - Tom? Tom,
我十分尊敬你
I have great respect for you
還有你在《先驅報》的工作
and the work you've done at the Herald.
但你能就她自己的表現來評述她嗎
But are you even capable of defining her on her own terms?
抱歉  前一秒她還是悲傷寡婦
I'm sorry. One minute she's playing the grieving widow
-下一秒  她又借題發揮  -正是
- and the next, she's riding on the coattails. - Case in point.
雖然這么說很過分
This may be an unseemly thing to say,
但很可能
but it's quite possible
她丈夫的死  是總統走了大運
her husband's death was the president's lucky day.
你在這里可以暢所欲言
You can say whatever you want in here.
不管你有什么感覺  有什么想法
Whatever your feeling, thinking.
我質疑你的能力
I'm questioning your ability.
我的能力
My ability?
能不能分辨有道理的多疑和...
To tell the difference between justifiable paranoia and--
你還用那個詞嗎
Do you use the word anymore?
"瘋狂"
"Madness?"
你對什么感到多疑
What do you feel paranoid about?
我自己吧
Myself, maybe.
我們為什么做我們做的事  為誰而做
Why we do what we do and for who?
誰更邪惡  醫生
Who's more evil, Doctor,
發令者還是執行者
the taskmaster or the tasked?
你覺得弗蘭西斯·安德伍德背叛了你嗎
Do you feel like Francis Underwood betrayed you?
我覺得我在想是誰背叛了他
I guess I'm wondering who betrayed him.
你覺得呢
Who do you think?
你嗎
You?
我不知道我們的治療是否還能幫我
I don't know if these sessions are helping me anymore.
你為什么給我開藥  醫生
Why are you trying to drug me up, Doctor?
我覺得你該考慮一下
I think you should consider it.
氯氮平
Clozapine.
你肯定知道那會把人變成什么樣
You must know what that does to a person.
現在又有了新的抗精神病藥物  道格
They're a newer class of antipsychotics, Doug.
副作用
The side effects
不像以前的那些那么嚴重了
are not as sensational as some of the older ones.
你不非得這樣受罪的
You don't have to suffer like this.
據我所知
From my understanding,
光是副作用就能讓你顯得
the side effects themselves can make you look--
我又得問  你是否還用"瘋狂"這個詞
And again, I'm asking you if you use this word "mad."
你開玩笑嗎
Are you fucking kidding me?
什么
Pardon?
你要一邊看表
You're gonna talk to me about side effects
一邊跟我聊副作用嗎
while you look at your fucking clock?
不  你說得對  抱歉
No, you're right. I'm sorry.
我們還是明天下午繼續吧
We're gonna have to take this up tomorrow afternoon.
這個話題要重大得多
This is a much bigger conversation.
不  我就現在說
No, I'm talking now.
抱歉  但你的時間到了
I'm sorry, but your time is up.
我才不在乎時間
I don't give a fuck about the time.
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper.
我很高興你終于決定
I'm glad that you finally decided
好好利用你在這里的時間
to take advantage of your time here,
但你清楚規矩
but you know the rules.
我哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
斯坦普先生  拜托
Mr. Stamper, please.
我也不想叫人來  但我會的
I don't want to have to call someone, but I will.
這太扯了
This is bullshit.
你舅舅可不高興
Your uncle is not happy.
你知道你有多少次
Are you aware of how many of your sentences
張口就說他怎樣嗎
start with you quoting him?
他是對的
He's right.
這場鬧劇適得其反
This circus backfired.
-我覺得你很棒  -你舅舅覺得
- I thought you were wonderful. - Your uncle thinks
-我們惡化了本就糟糕的局面  -媽媽
- we've made a bad situation worse. - Mom.
現在我成了這事的臉面人物了
Now I'm the face of this thing.
我們會利用這點幫我們的
Which we will use to our advantage.
她直接點了我們的名字
She called us out by name.
我們想怎么扭轉輿論都行
We can spin it any way we want.
在國會想辦法
Work the Congress.
就算她否決了法案  他們也能推翻她的決策
Even if she vetoes the bill, they can override it.
她反應過度了
She overreacted.
-還讓我出了丑  -相信我
- And it made a fool of me. - I'm telling you,
你贏了
you won.
她覺得是她贏了
She thinks she did.
我認得那個表情  相信我
I know that expression, trust me.
她都想不好自己是麥克白夫人還是麥克白
She can't decide if she's Lady Macbeth or Macbeth.
-接下來讓你舅舅處理  -不
- Your uncle takes it from here. - No.
這對我沒什么私人感情
This isn't personal for me,
不像對你和比爾舅舅
not like it is for you and Uncle Bill.
你知道他討厭關注
You know he hates the spotlight,
不管是對我們誰
for any of us.
他更喜歡老式的手腕
Prefers an old school way of dealing with things.
-我  -別以為你什么都知道了
- I... - And don't think you know everything.
因為不是的
Because you don't.
讓我跟比爾舅舅談談
Let me talk to Uncle Bill.
他住進了海亞當斯酒店
He's taken a suite at the Hay-Adams.
弗蘭克以前的房間
Frank's old room.
我是道格·斯坦普  聯邦檢察官女士
It's Doug Stamper, Madam US Attorney.
-你怎么拿到這個號碼的  -別掛
- How did you get this number? - Don't hang up.
你再打來  讓你的律師打去我辦公室
The next call I expect is from your lawyer. In my office.
那可不好
You really shouldn't.
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper,
-這非常...  -我要撤供
- this is highly-- - I'm going to recant.
你在聽嗎
Are you there?
是的
Yes.
我要說明事情會怎么發展
I'm going to lay out how it's going to go.
如果我說錯了  你就打斷我
And you stop me at any point if I'm wrong.
但我要撤供
But I'm going to recant.
所以你需要換新的檢察官
Which means you're going to need a new prosecutor.
因為你得回避
Because you're going to have to recuse yourself
好出庭指證我
so you can testify against me.
我們的這通電話
And this call we're on,
對你會不利的
is not going to look very good for you.
你在法庭上說的一切都會被判為傳聞
Anything you say in court will be ruled hearsay.
法官
And the judge,
如果心情好會要求出示更多證據
if he's in a good mood, is going to ask for more evidence,
而你和你的新檢察官卻拿不出
and you and your new prosecutor aren't going to have any.
等等  等等
Et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
這個案子將無法成就你的事業
This case isn't going to make your career.
能改變你人生的案子
The case that's going change your life
是對克萊爾·安德伍德的起訴
is the prosecution of Claire Underwood.
真是可怕
It's gruesome,
這里發生的事
what's gone on here.
我親自檢查了所有登記簿
I checked all the log books myself.
還詢問過行政管家
I spoke with the executive housekeeper.
她詢問了員工  沒人知道怎么回事
She interviewed the staff. Nobody knows anything.
那他的戒指是神奇地出現在了他的床上
So his ring just appeared on his bed by magic?
我感覺
My feeling is,
我們該關注的不是這件事本身
it's not the fact of it that we should be focusing on.
而是
But...
它意味著什么
what it means.
告訴我  馬克  什么樣的人會掘開他的墳墓
Tell me, Mark. What kind of people dig up a man's grave
把戒指從他冰冷僵硬的手指上
and remove a ring from his cold...
摘下來
hard finger?
就是那些在拿弗蘭西斯的赦免
The same people that are generating this drum beat
和你的離婚請求做文章的人
about Francis' pardon and your divorce.
是你在刺激他們
You are daring them.
是你把事情鬧大了  現在他們不肯罷休了
You've turned it into a spectacle, and now they will not stop.
相信我  這些人不會罷休的
Believe me. These people will not rest.
你得做出彌補
You need to make amends.
為對她的輕慢嗎
For slighting her?
-為指出他們嗎  -你得給他們點什么
- For identifying them? - You have to give them something.
-我不相信這份法案  -該死的
- I don't believe in the bill. - Oh, goddamn it!
這份法案  你在聽嗎
This bill. Are you listening?
你想把余下的任期都消耗在
Do you want to spend the rest of your presidency
維護你死去的丈夫
defending your dead husband,
和他的
defending his...
行為上嗎
deeds?
因為他們會確保
Because they will make sure
你在白宮不論清醒還是沉睡的
that every waking and even sleeping moment
每一時每一刻都無法擺脫他
of your time in the White House is about him!
為過去一百天里的事做彌補
Make amends for the last hundred days.
你就能擁有接下來的四年
Then you can have the next four years.
你周末
When you present the
去志遠俱樂部頒獎學金時
scholarship at the Take Aim Club this weekend,
安奈特·謝潑德也會到場
Annette Shepherd will be there.
她是董事會成員  他們都捐款
She's on the board. They're all donors.
跟你的老朋友一起出席
Appear with your old friend...
把法案簽了
and sign this bill.
我可以幫你的
You know, I can help you...
在謝潑德兄妹那里  我會跟他們打交道
with the Shepherds. I know how to talk to them.
請跟我解釋一下  你為什么覺得
And please, please explain to me why you thought...
昨天提拔那個
putting that elevated intern
實習生去接待媒體對你有好處
in front of the press yesterday serves you.
-因為她誠實  -我準備了米奇·格雷澤
- Because she's honest. - I had Mitch Glazer lined up.
-他有30年的...  -因為她不是米奇
- He's got 30 years of-- - Because she's not Mitch.
因為我知道你趕走了肖恩
Because I know you pushed out Sean.
肖恩·杰弗瑞斯不愿說實話
Sean Jeffries had a hard time telling the truth.
你的那版實話嗎
Your truth?
是的  維系你權力的版本
Yes, the one that keeps you in power.
現在怎么
And now what?
你拿她的天真換他的野心嗎
We've traded his ambition for her naïveté?
我相信她
I believe her.
別人也會的
And so will everyone else.
-抱歉  你需要我...  -不
- I'm sorry, do you need me to-- - No, no,
我其實是來找你的
actually, I was looking for you.
我想為昨天的事道歉
I wanted to apologize for yesterday.
不  沒事的
No, please.
-我很高興你能幫忙  -好吧
- I was happy to have your help. - Okay.
你知道肖恩不會回來了吧
You know Sean's not coming back, right?
我聽說了
I heard.
總統肯定是看中了你的哪一點
The president must see something in you.
你覺得是什么
What do you think that is?
這是個很棒的機會
It was an amazing opportunity.
我聽說這個位置
And I've heard there are
有一些很不錯的候選人
some wonderful candidates for the position.
是啊
Yeah.
在確定之前
Well, until then...
你繼續
why don't you to continue on
做代理新聞發言人吧
as acting press secretary.
當然  好  先生
Of course. Yes, sir.
謝謝你和總統
And thank you and the president.
你相信她嗎  斯圖爾特小姐
Do you believe in her, Miss Stewart?
我相信
I do.
我問是因為
I ask because...
要知道有一些厲害的勢力
I want you to know there are powerful forces out there
很想看她失敗
that are invested in seeing her fail.
所以你會聽到謠傳  和暗示
So you're gonna hear rumors. You're gonna hear innuendos.
你得照你的要點講
You'll need to stick to your talking points.
別被些不懷好意的問題帶溝里去
Not get lured off-track with, what, salacious questions.
我明白
I understand.
現在  我算是幕僚長
Right now, I'm the de facto chief of staff.
所以  如果你需要
So, if you need...
幫助或建議
help or advice,
你知道去哪找我
you know where to find me.
祝你好運
Good luck.
謝謝
Thank you.
洛杉磯外的圣費爾南多谷起火了
There's a fire burning in the Valley outside of Los Angeles.
所以基金會就派志愿者過去
So, the Foundation sends volunteers in,
讓他們加入應用
we sign them up for the app.
在貝爾波特加入的人有多少
How many signed up in Bellport?
區域內外大概有五萬部手機
In and around the area, close to 50,000 phones.
除了大火  還有狹長地帶的洪水
But beside the fires, there's flooding in the Panhandle.
大雨已持續數日
It's been raining for days.
北達科他州一條管線爆裂
There's a pipeline that's burst in North Dakota.
這是我外甥想的
And my nephew came up with this?
是基于已有技術  但是
Well, it's based on pre-existing technology, but...
他看到了潛力
he saw the potential.
基本上  他們交出了自己的手機
Essentially they're handing over their phones,
你也知道
which as you know,
那個現在基本上就是他們自身的一部分了
is basically an extension of the self at this point.
鄧肯稱之為"我們靈魂的石棺"
Duncan calls them "the sarcophagi of our souls."
我們能采集手機信息
We'll be crawling peoples' phones.
你可以決定大家什么時候看到什么
You get to decide what people see and when.
弗蘭克是因為這風景才選這里住的嗎
Did Frank take this room because of the view?
好像是吧
Yes, I think he did.
你尊敬他
You respected him.
你怕他嗎
Did you fear him?
是的
Yes.
但你總能知道你和他的立場
But you always knew where you stood with him.
她呢
And her?
永遠不知道
You never know.
工廠的工人用應用了嗎
Did the workers at the plant sign up for the app?
-大都用了  -很好
- Most of them did, yes. - Good.
很好
Good.
我很高興你來為我們工作  賽斯
I'm glad you're working with us, Seth.
你對安德伍德夫婦的了解
Your perspective, when it comes to the Underwoods,
還有我外甥
my nephew.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
退休探員嗎
Retired agents?
他們現在是自由職業了
They're freelance now.
為奈克西斯安保工作  很多人都這樣
Working for Nexis Securities. A lot of guys do it.
據說他倆這一周來都在
Apparently these two have been on the ground in Gaffney
加夫尼
for the last week or so.
-誰雇傭的  -我們還不知道
- Hired by who? - We don't know yet.
但他們掙的錢夠多  其中一人剛在
But they're making enough so that one of them just purchased
切薩皮克灣買了第二棟房子
a second home on the Chesapeake Bay.
他們
They...
闖進了您在加夫尼的住所  女士
broke into your Gaffney residence, ma'am.
什么  特勤局呢
What? Where was Secret Service?
我怎么沒收到通知
And why wasn't I alerted?
因為沒人收到通知
Because no one was alerted.
他們什么都沒動
They left it completely untouched,
至少看上去是的
as far as anyone can tell.
那你怎么知道有人去過
How did you know anyone was there, then?
一個失眠的鄰居
An insomniac neighbor
看到屋里有手機屏幕的亮光
who spotted the light from a phone screen inside.
拍照吧
Taking pictures, I'm assuming.
天吶
My, my, my.
加夫尼的夜生活豐富起來了
Night life in Gaffney certainly has picked up.
從我小時候開始的
Started when I was a kid.
只要有機會
Whenever the opportunity would present itself,
我就會伸手到衣兜里去  看能找到什么
I'd slip my hand into a coat pocket to see what I could find.
陌生人的衣兜是窺視其靈魂的窗口
A stranger's pocket is a window into his soul.
你發現了什么
And what did you find?
安全套
Condoms.
薄荷糖  鑰匙
Mints. Keys.
你把你發現的東西偷走了嗎
Did you steal what you found?
沒偷薄荷糖  那太殘忍了
Not the mints. Because that would be cruel.
是你嗎
Was that you...
去機場路上那事
on the way to the airport?
是想教訓她嗎
Were you trying to teach her a lesson?
-去找比爾吧  -拜托
- Talk to Bill. - Come on.
我已經跟他談過了
I already did.
-她遲到了  -她是總統嘛
- She's late. - Yeah, she's the president.
你就是對強勢女人心軟
You know, you have a weakness for strong women.
真的
No, really.
你覺得她們需要你幫助
You think they need your help.
不是吧
Really?
-還抽呢  -不
- Still? - No, no.
我現在嚼口香糖了
I chew now.
我就是喜歡
I just like to...
玩這個
play with this.
等等
Wait.
她來了
She's here.
總統女士  鄧肯·謝潑德
Madam President, Duncan Shepherd.
-你好  -克萊爾
- Hello. - Claire.
安奈特
Annette.
你見過鄧肯了
I see you've met Duncan.
-我們走吧  -好
- Shall we? - Yes.
可不許再抽我手了
Don't ever recoil from me again.
50多棒啊
Ain't 50 nifty?
你上次把我拉進洗手間里
I think the last time you dragged me into a bathroom,
好像是為了炫耀你的吻痕
it was to show off your hickey.
我覺得你哥哥不會收手的  安奈特
I don't think your brother is gonna let up, Annette.
除非我直接俯首稱臣
Until he gets his ring kissed directly, I think.
這讓我想起了你曾經的丈夫
Reminds me of someone you were married to.
不  比爾和弗蘭西斯可很不一樣
No. Bill and Francis are very different people.
是啊
Agreed.
我睡過他一次
You know I slept with him once.
你哥哥嗎
Your brother?
你丈夫
Your husband.
我知道
I know.
有意思
Interesting.
不過想來  也不奇怪
Though, come to think of it, I guess it makes sense.
什么
What does?
你們的婚姻不介意那些
That your marriage allowed for that.
那是98年的競選
Well, it was the '98 campaign.
弗蘭西斯的對手勢頭很猛
Francis was facing a robust challenger,
你們在華府的哪個籌款宴會上碰面了
and there you were at some DC fundraiser or other.
是在聯合車站
It was at the Union Station,
-東大堂  -對
- East Hall. - Yes.
你晃著手里的支票簿
And there you were, dangling your checkbook.
所以聽上去像是挺不錯的交易
So, it sounds like a favorable transaction all around.
-他是那么跟你說的嗎  -我從不問細節
- Is that what he told you? - I never asked for details.
我當時是挺好奇
I mean, I was curious.
真的
I really was.
他吻技還不錯
He was a good kisser, I'll say that.
但其他的  太不給力了
But then the rest was so underwhelming.
感覺他的心沒全在那兒
Felt like he wasn't all there.
就好像他沒...
Like, he wasn't...
完全投入
all in, so to speak.
當然了  我第一個念頭...
Of course, my first thought, and...
大部分女人都會如此吧
isn't this true of most women?
我想會不會是我
Was to wonder if it was me.
我的床技是不是
Was I somehow less skilled
比我自以為的要差
than I like to believe I am?
這我就不知道了  安奈特
Well, I can't really answer to that, Annette.
我知道
I can.
是他
It was him.
而且
And...
我敢說他跟你也一向是如此
I bet it was never very different with you.
哪怕是你
Even you.
金發女神
The blonde goddess.
哪怕是跟你  對嗎
Even with you. Am I right?
我真的現在才意識到
It's really only dawning on me now.
你做出的犧牲
The sacrifice you made.
我都有點可憐你
I sort of pity you.
你這么多年來是怎樣有苦說不出
What you must have denied yourself all those years.
我現在就要讓你閉嘴了  安奈特
And this is where I tell you to shut your mouth, Annette.
你根本不懂婚姻
You don't know anything about marriage,
跟別說我的了
much less mine.
隨便你怎么安慰自己  克萊爾
Tell yourself whatever you want, Claire.
我們都清楚真相
We both know the truth.
他在走廊那邊的備餐廚房等你
He's waiting for you down the hall in the prep kitchen.
我哥哥
My brother.
我現在還會呢
I can still do it by the way.
你呢
Can you?
你錯過了晚餐
Well, you missed dinner.
你想吃什么  我可以讓他們給你做
I can have 'em make you whatever you like.
我不餓
I'm not hungry.
秘訣在于放多少
The secret here is how much
檸檬汁
lemon juice you put in.
能調和黃油
Balance out the butter.
大家都喜歡荷蘭汁
People and hollandaise.
覺得那是錢的味道
They think it tastes like money.
-酒店般的享受  -你想找什么
- A night at the hotel. - What where you looking for?
加夫尼宅邸里沒有什么值錢的東西
There's nothing in the Gaffney home of value.
弗蘭克做過些事
Frank did things.
你怎么
And you just, what?
就當沒看見嗎
Look the other way?
你沖我開的那一槍  這么魯莽不像你啊
That shot you took at me, it's not like you to be so reckless.
你不好嚇
You don't scare easy.
這事關國家的未來
The future of our country is at stake.
這聽上去
Does that sound...
做作嗎  天真嗎
pat to you, naive?
完全不會
No, not at all.
你以為我在五角大樓就沒朋友了嗎  克萊爾
Do you think I don't have friends at the Pentagon, Claire?
你或許想讓我的四年任期很不好過...
You may want to make my four years in office miserable--
我只是希望你按說好的做
All I want you to do is behave, as promised.
你可以去挖戒指  或其他你能挖到的東西
You can dig up a ring or whatever else you can get your hands on.
但那不代表
But that doesn't mean
我不會也讓你一樣不好過
I won't make your time a living hell as well.
雷蒙德·塔斯克有次說你
Raymond Tusk said about you one time,
我們是一起出席什么晚宴  他說...
some dinner we were at, he just said it--
我現在是應該
This is where I'm supposed to be
有點害怕聽到他說了什么
a little bit afraid of the answer,
-是吧  -他說"我不知道
- I suppose. - He said, "I don't know,
她真是個人
whether or not she's a person...
還是在扮演一個人"
or just playing the part of one."
我當時還覺得這話很奇怪  但或許這是真的
And I thought it was so strange at the time, but maybe it's true.
你真是
Just...
不通人情
unreachable.
我知道這對你很難
I know it'll be hard for you.
但你得平等地對待我  比爾
But you're going to have to treat me as an equal, Bill.
你怎么處理你丈夫的遺囑的
What did you do with your husband's will?
那是份可撤銷的信托
It was a revocable trust.
我都處理好了
All done.
我不是說那個
I'm not talking about that one.
我是說另一個
I'm talking about the other one.
新的那份
The new one.
道格·斯坦普肯定會想看到那份
Bet Doug Stamper would love to see the contents of that one.
上面寫了什么
What's in there anyway?
你竟不惜一切
That you would go to such lengths
讓他看不到
to keep him from it?
克萊爾·黑爾有個秘密
Claire Hale has a secret.
道格拉斯·斯坦普這會兒正在跟聯邦檢察官
Douglas Stamper is meeting with the US District Attorney
會面
as we speak.
他出來了  克萊爾
He's out, Claire.
他不會再回去了
And he's not going back in.
你需要我的幫助
Now, you need my help.
今晚晚些時候
Later tonight,
我要眼看著你簽署
I'm going to watch you sign that bill
你桌上的那份法案
that's sitting on your desk.
"對于死者
"To the dead,
王國毫無意義
a kingdom means nothing.
他們已經擁有安寧和永恒了"
They have their requiem and eternity."
是歌劇《麥克白》  不是戲劇
That's Macbeth. The opera, not the play.
你現在只需要出去
All you have to do now is just go on out there
跟你最久最親愛的朋友站在一起
with your oldest, dearest friend and...
把她的手高高地舉起來
hold her hand up high.
總統女士
Madam President.
你并不真認為美軍是無關緊要的吧[S03E02]
You don't really think the military is irrelevant?
我在我的法官室里
I watched your confirmation
觀看了你的聯合國大使提名表決
from my chambers for the UN.
不是我最好的時刻
Wasn't my finest hour.
笑得最響的[男]人...
Well, he who laughs loudest--
還是"笑到最后"
Or is it "laughs last"?
"最后"  是"女人"
"Last." "She."
-我是文森特·阿布佐  -第九巡回法院
- Vincent Abruzzo. - Ninth Circuit.
我很不適應這樣的場合
I am no good at functions like this.
我一般都在這樣的活動上找把椅子
I tend to find a chair at these things
然后就坐一晚上
and sit in it for the rest of the evening.
-總統女士  -嗯  很榮幸認識你
- Madam President. - Yes. Well, it's been a pleasure.
總統女士  容我說一句
Madam President, if I may say,
我很高興總統辦公室總算迎來一位女性
I'm so glad that we finally have a woman in the Oval Office.
雖然歷時很久  但...
The arc of history is long, but--
中年白人男子的統治結束了
The reign of the middle-aged white man is over.
比爾·謝潑德這樣不肯放手的人  必須下臺
The Bill Shepherds of the world who won't let go, have to go.
除了你  還有別人知道寄給他的那份文件嗎
Does anyone except you know about the document that came for him?
當然沒有
No, of course not.
因為如果有別人拿到了那份遺囑
Because if anyone else gets their hand on that will--
那完全是你知我知
That is strictly between us.
我們才剛發現他失蹤了
We only just discovered that he was missing.
我聯系了聯邦檢察官  才得知
I put a call into the US Attorney and was just informed
指控已撤銷
charges have been dropped.
這怎么可能
How is that even possible?
我幾天前以為自己丟了手機
I thought I'd lost my phone a couple of days ago, but...
但現在我可以確定
But now I'm certain that
是他拿走了  打電話做了筆交易
he took it and reached out to make a deal.
我可以選好大陪審團
I can have a grand jury impaneled
一周內就開始對證人進行取證
and we can be taking testimony from witnesses within a week.
你找了誰
Who do you have?
杜蘭特國務卿嗎
Secretary Durant?
還有別人
And others.
我相信不用我告訴你是非對錯
I'm sure I don't need to talk to you about what's right or wrong.
但依我的經驗  大部分人到最后
But in my experience, most people, in the end,
都會不惜一切地保護自己
will do whatever they need to, to save themselves.
你覺得你的勝算大嗎
Do you think you have a strong enough case?
那要看你的了
That depends on you.
如果我要拿自己冒險
If I'm gonna put myself on the line,
我需要知道你能贏
I need to know you're going to win.
這個城市可以很記仇
This can be a very unforgiving town.
我在給你重新開始的機會
I'm giving you a chance to start over.
-得了  -我可以拿豁免權
- Come on. - I can offer you immunity
換取你的證詞
for your testimony.
但是  當然了  斯坦普先生  我并不能就
But, Mr. Stamper, of course, I can't give you any guarantees
你或前總統的名聲做出擔保
when it comes to your reputation or that of the former president.
你得在公開法庭上作證
You would have to testify in an open court.
這是我們的條件
That is the deal.
我要咨詢下我的律師
I should consult with my lawyers.
謝謝你前來  斯坦普先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Stamper.
與我們一起支持達拉斯年輕女性
Join us in supporting the Dallas Scholarship Fund
獎學金基金
for Young Women:
志遠
Take aim.
看看這些了不起的面孔
Look at these marvelous faces.
她們是未來的面孔
The faces of our future.
我非常榮幸
And I am so, so honored
能夠向大家介紹
to be chosen to introduce to you
美國總統  克萊爾·安德伍德
the President of the United States, Claire Underwood.
我看著這些杰出的年輕姑娘
I look at these brilliant young women
激動得難以言表
and words fail me.
這是什么
What's this?
他們發給了我們這個  它們能干什么
They gave us these. What are they gonna do?
我可不喝那水
Yeah, I'm not drinking the water,
絕不  我告訴你
no fucking way, I'll tell you that.
實在不行我就去坎頓買
I'll go all the way to Canton to buy it, if I have to.
格雷森先生
And... Mr. Grayson,
關于這個應用  他還對你說了什么
what else did he tell you about the app?
沒說什么了  你可以上網去看
Nothing. You can go online and check it out.
因為我認識的很多人
'Cause a lot of people I know
在總統走后還是下載了
signed up for it even after the president left.
他說...
He said...
格雷森先生嗎
Mr. Grayson?
對  他
Yeah, him.
它們能讓我們在事發前就知道
That they were gonna tell us what was gonna happen
-要發生什么  -那怎么說
- before it happens. - How?
我不知道
Look, I don't know.
伊薩卡在哪里
Ithaca's, like, where?
希臘有一個
There's one in Greece.
紐約州北也有一個
And the other's in upstate New York.
猜猜哪個是我的家鄉
Guess which one I'm from.
是一份報紙  每周印發一期
It's a paper, it comes out once a week.
這是不可避免的
It was going to happen,
因為之前就發生過
because it happened before.
我們都上報到環保署了  但是
We complained all the way to the EPA, but...
沒辦法
whatever.
只不過這次的爆炸比較嚴重
Only this time the explosion was bad.
是啊  死了人  公司早就知道
And yeah, some guys died. And the company knew.
他們知道的
They knew.
歡迎回家
Welcome home.
真巧  我剛煮上咖啡
Good timing. I just put on coffee.
現在喝咖啡有點晚了吧
A little late for coffee.
我們有好多要談呢
Well, we have so much to talk about.
我很高興你出來了  道格
I'm glad you're out, Doug.
我都不知道你為什么會進去
I don't know what you were doing in there.
聯邦檢察官怎么樣了
How's the US Attorney?
杜蘭特國務卿在商談她的出庭
Secretary Durant's negotiating her appearance.
如果
And if...
凱茜被勸說不去了呢
Cathy should somehow be dissuaded?
-不發聲了呢  -那一切都不了了之
- Silenced? - Then it all goes away.
是啊  但他們還是會想知道
Yes, but they'll still want to know
誰知道什么  什么時候
who knew what, when.
我挺清楚的
I feel pretty clear.
你覺得是我叫你背鍋的
You think it was me who asked you to take the fall
-因為是我開的口  -他告訴我是你了
- just because I said the words, right? - He told me it was you.
-他悄悄對我說的  -你就信了
- He whispered it in my ear. - And you believed him.
你總是相信他
Like you always believed him.
我是這么想的  佐伊·巴恩斯自殺了
Well, here's what I believe. Zoe Barnes killed herself--
其他的事我會得到赦免
And I expected to be pardoned for the rest.
他死后  我一直受到束縛
Since his death, my hands have been tied.
但我認為上天給了我們一份禮物
But I believe the universe has given us a gift.
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
這么說吧
Well...
我們都失去了一個
We both lost someone
改變了我們人生軌跡的人
who shaped the course of our lives.
有好的改變  也有壞的
For good, but also for ill.
現在我們
And now here we are
意外地自由了
unexpectedly free.
可以選擇不一樣的方法
To take a different tack.
我們想做什么都行  道格
We can do whatever we want, Doug.
我們的命運一直糾纏在一起
And we've been entwined, you and I,
不管愿不愿意
like it or not,
這幾十年來都是如此
for decades now.
但我覺得
But I think...
我們有權分道揚鑣了
we deserve to go our separate ways.
唯一的問題是
The only problem is
我們有個緊急的問題要處理
we have something urgent to attend to
凱茜·杜蘭特
called Cathy Durant.
然后我們就終于自由了
And then we can finally be free.
做我們真正想做的
Do what we really want.
做我們需要做的
Do what we need to do.
道格·斯坦普想要什么
What does Doug Stamper want?
你是想抹去他嗎
Are you trying to erase him?
因為你做不到
Because you can't.
我沒有別的意思
I'm not trying to do anything
只是想做好現任美國總統
except be the sitting President of the United States.
你不該認定
It's wrong to assume
弗蘭西斯的野心跟我的完全一致  道格
Francis's ambitions directly aligned with mine, Doug.
要想不被與他的可疑行為聯系在一起
The best way to not to be associated with his questionable deeds
就得做好事
is to do good.
至少我是打算這么做的
That's what I plan to do, anyway.
你覺得好笑  是嗎
Oh, you find that funny, do you?
是真的
Well, it's true.
我就不懂他看好了你什么
I never understood what he saw in you.
這副皮囊的確不錯
I mean the outside, sure.
但內心
But the inside...
-莉安的死  -不
- LeAnn's death. - No.
你根本沒在乎過她
You never cared for her.
并不非得如此
It wasn't necessary.
我也這么跟他說了
And I told him so.
但是...
And yet...
道格  幫個忙
Doug, do me a favor.
閉上眼睛
Close your eyes.
拜托
Please.
他把這個留給了你
He wanted you to have them.
這種事就你這個年紀來說
For this to happen at this point in your life,
預后并不樂觀
the prognosis is not good.
我知道
I know.
有人殺了弗蘭西斯
Somebody killed Francis,
卻不希望他死
and yet they don't want him to die.
我們最后一次通話的那晚
That last night, the last time we spoke,
就是我在總統辦公室里拒接了他的電話
was when I declined his phone call in the Oval Office.
已經快兩個月了  他不想再等了
It had been close to two months, and he was tired of waiting.
于是他自己跑來了白宮
So he showed up here in the White House.
像個小賊
Like a thief.
當時好可怕
It was terrifying.
他暴跳如雷  說話都不清楚了
He was furious, slurring his words.
"你怎么就不能乖乖聽話  克萊爾"
"Why can't you do as you're told, Claire?"
我告訴世人他死在了我們的床上
I told the world that he died in our bed,
但那不是事實
but that's not the truth.
我那晚上把自己鎖在了我的房間里
I locked myself in my room that night,
早上醒來時  發現他死在了自己房里
woke up in the morning and found him dead in his.
他們殺了他  好讓我閉嘴
They killed him to shut me up.
我必須徹底埋葬弗蘭西斯
I need to bury Francis, once and for all.
簽字還需要人幫忙嗎
Do you need help signing it?
別  比爾  謝潑德  夠了
No. Bill. Shepherd, enough.
其實  我有個條件
I actually have one condition.
放回去
Put it back.
根據美國勞工部發布的10月就業數據
新增非農就業崗位25萬  失業率3.7%
工資增長速度為2008年以來最快
許多特朗普的支持者認為  這些數字
一要歸功于共和黨2017年末通過的減稅法案
二要歸功于特朗普政府一系列的去監管措施
在過去兩年中  特朗普政府信守共和黨"小政府""少插手"的理念
大幅度廢除聯邦行政法規和監管條例
到今年7月為止  白宮共廢除176項監管性法規  節省開支230億美元
其中環保署在2018年就取消/廢除了10項法規
而這一數字預計會在2019年增長到30項
但去監管在刺激經濟增長的同時  也增加了發生環保災難的可能
今年三月  美國英國多家媒體揭露  在2016年大選期間
一家名為"劍橋分析"的公司在用戶不知情的情況下
從臉書上獲取用戶個人信息  并將其賣給特朗普競選團隊
新聞曝光后  臉書股價大幅下滑  執行總裁扎克伯格
也不得不到國會山作證  接受議員們的嚴詞問詢
此后臉書和其它一些網站在用戶隱私政策上進行了改進
過去十年中  互聯網和移動終端在美國政治生活中發揮的作用越來越大
但同時也帶來了一系列的嚴重問題
目前美國共和黨和民主黨都對社交網絡公司的一些操作有很大意見
不過雙方所關注的問題不盡相同
民主黨指責社交網絡上假新聞泛濫  影響了選舉結果
而共和黨則抱怨硅谷的公司在網絡上刻意打壓保守派言論
因此要求立法監管社交網絡的呼聲越來越大
硅谷數家大公司的老板都曾被叫到國會山接受議員們的問詢
支持和反對監管的兩種力量也正在激烈較量中  尚未分出勝負
美國有著非常嚴格的環保法規  聯邦環保署權力很大
下屬的環保執法機構犯罪調查處雖然只有200名左右的探員
但是這些環保先鋒有非常獨立的執法權  可以攜帶槍支  執行逮捕
2017年聯邦環保署的執法隊伍共罰沒收繳了50億美元的款項
在罪案調查過程中  環保署的執法部門也會同其它聯邦執法部門合作
不過劇中被調駐到國防部的情況在現實生活中還不曾出現
環保署自身執法權限很大  在對付大公司的時候一般也不需要五角大樓介入
近年來倒在環保署鐵拳下的最大一個目標是德國的大眾公司
由于在尾氣排放問題上作假  在環保署的調查下
大眾公司被罰款28億美元  并支付15億美元的補償款
涉案的一名公司高管和一名工程師也被判入獄
因為共和黨的去監管主張  在特朗普主政之后  環保署力量被大幅削弱
其下屬的執法部門調查的案件也照往年有很大幅度的減少